POURIA NAVABPOUR based in Turin, ITALY

+39 331 411 2043 pouria.navabpour@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/pouria-navabpour github.com/Pouria-N pouria-navabpour.com Birth date: 05July 1988

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I'm a multidisciplinary designer and planner with a background in architecture, urban planning. Now transitioning into **front-end web development**, I'm expanding my skill set into the web world. I've learned and still learning **HTML**, **CSS**, **JavaScript**. And, I have used my knowledge to create my first project to present my portfolio. It was during my master's degree at Politecnico di Torino that my path began to realign with my early interests. Thanks to my tutor and life mentor, Professor Andrea Pollio, I was introduced to the deeper connections between technology and urbanism. Now, I'm committed to fully embracing the world of technology, aligning my career with my lifelong passion.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

TEACHING ASSISTANT, POLITECNICO DI TORINO | OCT 2024 - DEC 2024

Supported students through workshops and projects focused on decision-making strategies in post-carbon cities. Provided under Prof. Torabi | Teaching Assistant.

• TECHNICAL DOCUMENTATION SPECIALIST, PROGRETT, TORINO | SEP 2023 - MAY 2024

I worked as a GIS/CAD technician using QGIS and AutoCAD to create design documentation and drawings for permits for fiber optic projects. Also, I created training videos for new staff. | Temporary work.

INTERIOR DESIGNER AND 3D VISUALIZER, VISIONARY HOME CO. - KISH ISLAND | MAR 2021 - AUG 2022

I worked as an Interior Architect to create architectural designs using 3ds Max, Corona Render engine, Photoshop, and AutoCAD in collaboration with clients and architects. | External collaboration contract.

ARCHITECTURAL DESIGNER AND 3D VISUALIZER, BORJ ZARIN CO. - TABRIZ | MAR 2020 - MAR 2021

I designed and visualized architectural concepts using 3ds Max, Corona Render engine, Photoshop, and AutoCAD in collaboration with clients and architects. | External collaboration contract.

ARCHITECTURAL VISUALIZER, TARH SABZ ANDISHE CO. - TABRIZ | SEP 2019 - AUG 2022

I produced high-quality 3D visualizations and renderings of architectural projects using 3Ds Max, the Corona Render engine, and Photoshop for client presentations and marketing materials. | Occasional Work.

• TECHNICAL OFFICE MANAGER, AZARSANAN CO. - TABRIZ | JUN 2014 - JUN 2016

I managed technical documentation like technical statements, minutes of meetings, and work progress. I was also responsible for the approvals and followed up on the paperwork. | Permanent Employment.

EDUCATION

POLITECNICO DI TORINO

Master's Degree in Territorial, Urban, Environmental and Landscape Planning | 2022 - 2024

Thesis: Technological Ambivalence in Urban Dashboards and their Digital Governance | GPA: 105/110

AZAD UNIVERSITY

Master's Degree in Architectural Engineering | 2016 - 2019

Thesis: Crafts Museum Design, Emphasizing Tus City Vernacular Capacity | GPA 16.33/20.00

AZAD UNIVERSITY

Bachelor's Degree in Civil Engineering | 2006 - 2011

GPA: 14.15/20.00

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Persian: Native | English: Fluent | Italian: Basic (in progress)

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- GIS & CAD: QGIS, AUTOCAD, REVIT ARCHITECTURE
- VISUALIZATION & GRAPHICS: 3DS MAX, BLENDER, LUMION, PHOTOSHOP
- **PROGRAMMING (in Progress):** HTML, CSS, JavaScript
- PRODUCTIVITY TOOLS: MICROSOFT OFFICE (WORD, EXCEL, POWERPOINT)

SOFT SKILLS

The ability of emotional intelligence, problem-solving, and adaptability are my strongest features. I demonstrate a strong ability to learn and adapt quickly and am capable to work successfully in teams, with attention to detail, ethics, and being result-oriented.